



Junior Python developer, with years of experience as a Field Service engineer in various fields, currently looking for a challenging opportunity to combine software development skills with domain expertise in a dynamic, technology-driven organization.

**EMAIL** 

jedrzej.grabala@gmail.com

#### **PERSONAL INFO**

**ADDRESS PHONE** 

ul. Szarych Szeregów 24/46 15-666 Białystok

**GITHUB WEBSITE** 

https://github.com/JGITSol https://jgit.solutions

+48500759624

## **SKILLS**

Python

Created multiple apps with proper local GUI(PySG), Authentication(with Google Cloud, as well as Azure), CRUD operations on files and databases, automated data entry proceses.

Deployment Methods Local(\*exe), web(streamlit via community cloud), web(Azure),

Driving license (class B in Poland) Gathered many years of experience driving in various countries, both abroad and local.

■ Fault diagnostics in compliance with technical documentation

PC & Electronics field repairs

# \*\*\*

2022-11 - present

2022-04 - 2022-07

### WORK HISTORY

# Freelancer Programmer (Business owner)

JGIT Solutions, Augustów, Polska

https://jgit.solutions

Project management, creating custom software for PC using Python with a dedicated user interface (web or local), creating websites, online stores, and payment gateways.

# **Thermographic Measurements Engineer**

SEAM Group Polska sp. z. o o., Warsaw

Performed thermographic measurements of electrical equipment in different industrial plants across Europe.

# **Field Service Engineer**

Medikol Systems sp z o. o., Poznań

2020-04 - 2022-04

Installation, maintenance, diagnostics and repairs of various X-ray medical equipment(ranging from mobile xray to CT's), for Samsung and DR GEM (as an official partner), and other brands - mostly legacy systems (out of warranty). Performing jobs on a tight schedule, contacting clients and writing technical reports on a daily basis. Work done mostly in North-East part of Poland.

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my CV to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act of May 10, 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in line with the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of April 27, 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation, GDPR).

# **Installation Engineer**

## Abplanalp, Warsaw

2019-11 - 2020-04

Instalation, maintenance, diagnostis and repairs of CNC machines made by HAAS, both lathes and milling machines. Conducting training of client's staff on basic operation and maintenance of HAAS products, updating software and providing technical support. Work done in Poland (whole territory).

# **Maintenance Engineer**

2018-08 - 2019-08

## Keylite RW Poland, Zambrów

Resolving complex production line issues, writing projects of possible future upgrades to improve machine park, scheduling maintenance, supporting mechanics in regards to control engineering faults, training staff on maintenance issues of production process. Job placed in Zambrów, Poland.

# **Assistant Surveyor**

2017-08 - 2018-04

#### **FACE Consultants Ltd, Huddersfield**

Performing various test in industrial complexes on concrete floor for compliance with british and international standards, calibration of custom made measuring devices, writing technical documentation on done tasks. Work done in West Europe- mostly UK, Ireland and Denmark.

## **Installation Technician**

2016-09 - 2017-04

## ATLIFT Adam Trypuć/ZEMD Jerzy Trypuć, Białystok

Instalation and disassembly of lifting devices, schematics based fault diagnostics and repair. Conducting safety tests and maintenance in two man teams. Job based in Białystok, Poland.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bialystok University of Technology, majoring in Automation and Robotics, undergraduate stationary studies.

2010-10 - 2014-02

I completed my undergraduate studies in Automation and Robotics with a specialization in Automation and Informatization of Industrial Processes, and defended my engineering thesis in June 2017. The title of my thesis was "Detection of Driver Fatigue Using Image Analysis."

#### **CERTIFICATES**

Qualifications: SEP (E) up to 1 KV, driving license category A and B

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English C1
- French A1

## **COURSES**

"Learn Robot Studio - Industrial Robot Jogging & Programming using Virtual Teach Pendant" done by Prag Robotics

2022-02

"Industrial Robotics - Mathematical models and practical applications" - done by Fabrizio Frigeni

2022-02

"Python 3 od Podstaw do Eksperta" ("Python 3 from Basics to Expert") -done by mr Arkadiusz Włodarczyk

2022-04

#### **HOBBY/INTEREST**

- LLM's(Large Language Models) and their use in common life
- IT and AI latest news
- Photography, digital art
- Motorbikes, Tourism

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my CV to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act of May 10, 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in line with the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of April 27, 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation, GDPR).